<PerfumeList>
	<Perfume>
		<itemId>1</itemId>
		<imageUrl>dolceAndGabbana.jpg</imageUrl>
		<name>DOLCE GABBANA Light Blue</name>
		<price>30.99</price>
		<description>
			A stunning perfume, overwhelming and irresistible like the joy of living. 
			Surprising and colored: the liveliness of Sicilian citron, 
			the happiness of Granny Smith apple, the spontaneity of bluebells. 
		</description>
		<quantity>5</quantity>
		<volume>3.3 OZ</volume>
		<category>Women</category>
		<promoCode>20CPNDG</promoCode>
	</Perfume>
	<Perfume>
		<itemId>2</itemId>
		<imageUrl>laVieStaBella.jpg</imageUrl>
		<name>La Vie Est Belle Perfume by Lancome</name>
		<price>95.55</price>
		<description>
		
			Iris is the key ingredient of the perfume, surrounded by orange blossoms and jasmine in the heart. 
			The compositions opening provides fruity flavour of black currant and pear, while the base is warm, 
			gourmand and powdery due to almond-like accords of tonka bean, praline, patchouli and vanilla. 
		
		</description>
		<quantity>10</quantity>
		<volume>4.0 Oz</volume>
		<category>Women</category>
		<promoCode>30CPNLVEB</promoCode>
	</Perfume>
	<Perfume>
		<itemId>3</itemId>
		<imageUrl>versaceTheDreamer.jpg</imageUrl>
		<name>Versace The Dreamer Cologne Perfume by Versace</name>
		<price>32.50</price>
		<description>
			Design House: Gianni Versace
			Fragrance Notes: wild flowers, linen, amber and tobacco.
			Recommended Use: casual
			
		</description>
		<quantity>12</quantity>
		<volume>3.3 Oz</volume>
		<category>Men</category>
		<promoCode>15CPNVTD</promoCode>
	</Perfume>
	<Perfume>
		<itemId>4</itemId>
		<imageUrl>stetsonSierra.jpg</imageUrl>
		<name>Coty Stetson Sierra</name>
		<price>73.33</price>
		<description>
			Stetson Sierra by Coty is a Aromatic Fougere fragrance for men. Stetson Sierra was launched in 1993. 
			Top notes are aldehydes, artemisia, caraway, juniper berries, green notes, basil and bergamot; 
			middle notes are carnation, jasmine, caraway, rose, pine tree needles and geranium; base notes are leather, 
			amber, patchouli, musk, oakmoss and cedar
		</description>
		<quantity>4</quantity>
		<volume>1.5 Oz 44ml</volume>
		<category>Men</category>
		<promoCode>50CPNCSS</promoCode>
	</Perfume>
	<Perfume>
		<itemId>5</itemId>
		<imageUrl>EternitybyCalvinKlein.jpg</imageUrl>
		<name>Eternity by Calvin Klein</name>
		<price>26.99</price>
		<description>
			Fragrance Type: Eau de Toilette Spray for Men
			Fragrance Type: Eau de Parfum Spray for Women
		</description>
		<quantity>7</quantity>
		<volume>3.4 Oz 100ml</volume>
		<category>Men and Women</category>
		<promoCode>12CPNECK</promoCode>
	</Perfume>
</PerfumeList>